{
  "level": 5,
  "unit": 1,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is the scattered remains of something.",
          "answer": "debris"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you say something with ____________ , you use special force or stress.",
          "answer": "emphasis"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ____________ is an unexpected meeting.",
          "answer": "encounter"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A son, father, and grandfather are three ____________ who all have a common family ancestor.",
          "answer": "generations"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Yesterday he ____________ , or showed a sign, that he was willing to help us.",
          "answer": "indicated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ____________ is a person who specializes in the study of things in nature.",
          "answer": "naturalist"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If a rock ledge is ____________ , it is steep.",
          "answer": "sheer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The magic show was ____________ because it was very impressive.",
          "answer": "spectacular"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If you can ____________ something, you have enough money to pay for it.",
          "answer": "afford"
        },
        { "prompt": "A ____________ is money borrowed.", "answer": "loan" },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is the amount of money left after all business costs have been paid.",
          "answer": "profit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you ____________ , you do well and become successful.",
          "answer": "prosper"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is the chance of loss or harm.",
          "answer": "risk"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is money set aside for the future.",
          "answer": "savings"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is ____________ , it is difficult to get or find.",
          "answer": "scarce"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are payments received for work done",
          "answer": "wages"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If you ____________ information, you get it from a source, such as the Internet.",
          "answer": "access"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you ____________ , you move forward or make progress.",
          "answer": "advance"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ____________ is a careful examination or study of something.",
          "answer": "analysis"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you ____________ something, you mention it as proof or evidence.",
          "answer": "cite"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ____________ is an opposing, or disagreeing, point of view.",
          "answer": "counterpoint"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are facts, figures, and other kinds of information.",
          "answer": "data"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are problems or disadvantages.",
          "answer": "drawbacks"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is having the ability to think in a logical way.",
          "answer": "reasoning"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
